<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Blog For All and None</title>
    <link>https://gemasphi.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Blog For All and None</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright><atom:link href="https://gemasphi.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Mr. Lee</title>
      <link>https://gemasphi.github.io/lee/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gemasphi.github.io/lee/</guid>
      <description>DISCLAIMER: If you&amp;rsquo;re a potential future employer, this story didn&amp;rsquo;t happen - it&amp;rsquo;s a bald-faced lie, a figment of my imagination. In fact, this story wasn&amp;rsquo;t even written by a human; it was generated by GPT-3.
 This story is a retelling of something that happened to me two years ago. Autobiographical in nature, I make no claims to the veracity nor the journalistic integrity of what you are about to read.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Schrodinger&#39;s Trip</title>
      <link>https://gemasphi.github.io/schrodingers-trip/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Feb 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gemasphi.github.io/schrodingers-trip/</guid>
      <description>[[Daylio]]
 Fake paris, sneaking into a show and camping in the park Botanical garden, Lingyin temple, walking through bamboo forests and Misty tea fields, going from tea village to tea village. At night, climbing the tree plantations in search of a place to camp Got deep learning code to work, walk around the west lake, left to Shanghai, went out Waking up destroyed, yuyu gardens, 1993 slaughterhouse, the bund，Michelin star restaurant Water towns, game of thrones eps with bingo and going out to linx Jing an temple, m50 and watching avatar Finished deep learning proposal, team lab, pudong and going to hongcun being scammed by the hostel, getting a taxi into the middle of hongcunzhen, a guard caught us and we bought a ticket to get rid of him, we sneaked into an abandoned house and camped there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://gemasphi.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Aug 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://gemasphi.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>A blog by a raving lunatic.
Do not believe a word you see here; every fact is slighty wrong, every argument fallacious and every story a lie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
